meramlm.com 2012-09-29

# MLM CLASSIFIEDS | MLM LEADERS | MLM DIRECTORIES | MLM LEADS | INDIA

|  |  | Privacy policy  
---  
By visiting www.meramlm.com, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy. This Policy is subject to change without notice and you should revisit this site frequently for the most current version of our privacy policy.   
Our Pledge to You, Our Customer and members  
you agree that all access to and use of this site and its content is at your own risk. www.meramlm.com will not be liable for any damage arising out of your access to, use of, or inability to use this site, or any errors or omissions in the content thereof. The materials in this site are provided "AS IS" and without warranties of any kind either expressed or implied.   
In our capacity as an interactive internet portal, we are required to collect information about you, including up-to-date, accurate and complete contact details. When you use one of our services with a form we ask for your full name, contact details and other relevant information to process your request.   
Use of Your Information  
Authorized employees of DNB Management Applications will use information collected on our Web site for below given purposes: 

  * We collect information to figure out how to improve our site by seeing which areas, features and products are most popular.
  * We may use personally identifiable information to contact you about your members account or other matters relating to our services.
  * We may also use personally identifiable information to send you our newsletter or e-mail or SMS messages regarding products or services we think you might be interested in. 
  * We share your information with our advertisers and affiliates for a given predefined purpose of marketing their product and services.
  * We may share your data with legal, financial, and other professional organizations for the purposes of investigating fraud or other offences.

Cookies and IP Addresses:  
We may use your IP address to identify you and your membership, gather broad demographic information about our users, diagnose problems with our server, and administer the Site. The Site uses cookies to keep track of your membership tools and to make sure you do not see the same ad repeatedly. We use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests and to save your password so you do not have to re-enter it each time you visit the Site. We also provide an option to log out should you be using an insecure or publicly shared computer.   
We use outside ad companies to display ads on the Site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of the Site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad companies, and we do not have access to this information.   
Links  
This Site contains links to other websites not owned or controlled by Mera **MLM**. Hence, we are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. Please ensure you review the privacy policies of the websites that you visit.  
Use of Our Information  
you understand that www.meramlm.com must protect its intellectual property, including its patents, trademarks, and copyrights. Therefore, no license to www.meramlm.com intellectual property has been granted by this Internet site.   
Maintenance of Accurate Information  
Procedures has been established to ensure that our product and promotional information is correct and accurate in keeping with reasonable standards. We are committed to respond to requests to correct inaccurate information in a timely manner.

If you have additional questions or comments of any kind, or if you see anything on our Web site that you feel is inappropriate, please contact us by sending an e-mail to info@dnb-ma.com
